这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell?
嘿，你听到了吗?
Hey, did you hear that?
听起来像炸弹爆炸。
Sounded like a bomb went off.
没有，但我听到警笛声，以为他们是来抓你的。
No, but I heard police sirens and thought maybe they were coming for you.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
我被叫去了。
I got called in.
老板不信任恩佐来经营这家店。
Boss doesn't trust Enzo to run the shop.
生活小常识。
Shocker.
今天是佐伊的生日，奥兰多。
It's Zoey's birthday, Orlando.
我这么做是为了谁，金?
Who else am I doing this for, Kim?
我不能失去这份工作。他们到处裁员。
I can't lose this job. They're laying people off left and right.
支票跟以前不一样了。
Checks aren't what they used to be.
听……我想我们今年要去我妈妈家过圣诞节。
Listen... I think we're gonna go to my mom's for Christmas this year.
我以为你只是在考虑。
I thought you were just thinking about it.
我想了想，决定了。
Well, I thought about it, and I decided.
我今天真的真的不想这么做。
I really, really didn't want to do this today.
但今天是你选择我们而不是工作的日子而不是你自己的日子。
But today was the one day for you to choose us over work and not make it about yourself.
佐伊的日子。
Zoey's day.
你还要惩罚我多久?
How long are you gonna keep punishing me for?
我们什么都试过了。
We have tried everything.
我就是做不到。
And I just can't.
我让佐伊中午给你打电话，我们可以好好相处。
So, I'll have Zoey call you at noon, and you and I can play nice.
如果你能腾出时间陪她。
If you can make the time for her.
嗯。
Hmm.
玩棋盘，不是我。
Play the board, not me.
耐心,老黄狗。
Patience, Old Yeller.
嗯…这就是你的行动吗，行动杰克逊?
Hmm... Is that your action, Action Jackson?
局长让我提醒你别把你的希爱力忘在外面。
And Chief wanted me to remind you to stop leaving your Cialis out.
显然，杰克以为是止痛药-所以他取消了家长会。
Apparently, Jake thought they were Advil, - and had to cancel his PTA meeting.
我知道你年纪大了会忘事，但是…我会永远记得你要被骂的样子。
I know you're forgetting things as your age, but, you know... I'll always remember the ass-whooping you're about to get.
吹牛，吹牛。
Oh, big talk, big talk.
嗯…
Hmm...
在你把手拿下来之前，你确定要这么做吗?
Before you take your hand off, you sure you want to do that?
好吧，做个英雄。
Okay, be a hero.
你这傻逼知道什么叫英雄吗?
What the hell does your broke down ass know about being a hero?
比你想知道的要多。
Ah, more than you'd like to know.
我们认识多久了?现在多长时间?六个月?
We've known each other for, what? How long now? Six months?
真的吗?你还要再来一次吗?
Really? Are you going to do this again?
我转学已经四个月了。
It's been four months since my transfer.
看起来要长得多。
Seems like so much longer.
你还在犯那些该死的菜鸟错误。
And you're still making those damn rookie mistakes.
将军。
Checkmate.
再来一次。不，三局两胜。
Let's go again. Nah, best of three.
-不，我已经赢过两次了。-好吧，五局两胜
- No, I already won twice. - All right, best of five.
——嘿,家伙。——是的。
- Hey, guys. - Yep.
我们有一个10-80。尼尔公园发生爆炸。
We got a 10-80. Explosion at Neil Park.
佐伊熊。你了?
Zoey bear. You up?
第一个又进来了。
First one in again.
早上好,女士们。
Good morning, ladies.
该起床了。
Time to wake up.
起床了，辛迪·卢。
Rise and shine, Cindy Lou.
早上好。
Top of the morning to ya.
好吧。
All right.
我们为您节省IT。我能为您做些什么?
We Save You IT. How can I help?
我的互联网去世了。
My-my internet has passed away.
好吧，看看能不能让它起死回生。
All right, let's see if we can't bring that back to life.
-你在路由器附近吗?——路由器?
- Are you near your router? - Router?
对，就是那个有闪烁灯的盒子。
Yeah, you know, the box with the blinking light.
那不是电脑吗?
Isn't-isn't that the computer?
不，小姐，是另一个闪着灯的盒子。
No, miss, the other box with the blinking light.
是的。
Yes.
好吧……让我们试着重启路由器。
All right... let's try and restart that router.
把它打开，等一下。
Flip it back on and give a sec.
了,猫!
Off, kitty!
她听起来很可爱。
Ooh, she sounds cute.
——没什么。-如果你相信我，我可以帮你在近路上节省很多时间。
- Nothing. - Well, if you trust me, I could save you a lot of time on a shortcut.
近路?
Mm, shortcut?
你知道，有时候我开车的时候，我喜欢走风景优美的路线。
You know, sometimes, when I'm driving, I like to take the scenic route.
其他时候，越快越好。
Other times, faster is better.
你说呢?
What do you say?
我们走捷径吧。
Let's try the shortcut.
好了，开始吧。
All right, here we go.
好吧。
All right.
顽皮的,淘气的。
Naughty, naughty.
你是怎么做到的?
How'd you do it?
有些人管这叫魔术，我管这叫客户服务，小姐。
Well, some people call it magic, I just call it customer service, miss.
其他人则认为这是非法的。
Others call it illegal.
哦，叫我小姐。
Oh, calling me miss.
你知道怎么让老女人感觉年轻。
You know how to make an old gal feel young.
打完电话之后还有调查，如果你喜欢我的服务。
Well, there's survey after this call, if you enjoyed my service.
顺便说一句，“密码”不是一个好密码。
And by the way, "password" isn't a good password.
——啊……-谢谢，女士。祝你今天愉快。
- Ah... - Thank you, ma'am. Have a nice day.
哇!他拍摄……哦，他得分了，观众都疯了!
Whoa! He shoots... Oh, he scores, and the crowd goes wild!
说真的，你是怎么做到的?
Man, like, how do you do it, for real?
这叫魅力，兄弟。
It's called charm, bro.
-一些你一无所知的事。-我什么都不知道?
- Something you know nothing about. - Oh, I know nothing?
我以前在孩子们的派对上表演魔术，朋友。
I used to do magic at kids' parties, my friend.
-真是魅力四射啊。-滚出城去真的吗?
- That is charm intensive. - Get out of town. Really?
-我女儿喜欢魔术。-是啊，她当然喜欢
- My daughter loves magic. - Yeah, of course she does.
每个人都喜欢一点点…花招。
Everyone's a sucker for a little... sleight of hand.
哇，伙计，太棒了。
Whoa, dude, that was good, man.
嗯,对的。在这里认识熟女也太变态了。
Eh, right. It's a sick spot to meet MILFs, too.
不过,我是认真的。如果玛丽发现你又迟到了，她会生气的。
I'm serious, though. Mary's going to be pissed if she finds out you came in late again.
真的吗?比让她发现你黑了客户的系统更重要吗?
Really? More than if she found out you just hacked a client's system?
我什么都没有。让顾客满意。
I took nothing. Left a customer happy.
啊,操。
Ah, fuck it.
说到快乐……看来老板给我们留了几份礼物。
Oh, speaking of happy... Looks like the boss left us a couple gifts.
-真的吗?-是的。
- No shit, really? - Yeah.
真的吗?
Really?
我想她是有价值的。
I guess she's good for something.
哦,不错。
Ooh, nice.
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell?
我在谷歌的朋友刚买了台笔记本电脑。
You know, my buddy at Google just got a laptop.
是的，我们有黑球。
Yeah, and we got black balls.
该死，伙计，有什么区别?
Shit, man, what's the difference?
机器随时会把我们淘汰。
Machines are gonna render us obsolete any second now.
也许擦窗户会是我们的下一份工作。
Maybe cleaning windows will be our next gig.
没有地狱。
Hell no.
我是说，你恐高吗，兄弟?
I mean, you afraid of heights, bro?
——地狱耶!-是啊，也许我也该这么做
- Hell yeah! - Yeah, I probably should have been, too.
你觉得我是怎么拿到这个的?
How do you think I got this?
-我觉得这样问太没礼貌了。
- Well, I thought it was too rude to ask.
不,来吧。
No, come on.
我17岁的时候在建筑工地摔了一跤。
It was a construction gig fall when I was 17.
你知道吗，你以为最糟糕的是撞击，但不是的。
You know, you'd think the worst part would be the impact, but no.
这是高高在上，然后摔在地上的耻辱。
It is the shame of being on top, and then fall on your ass in the dirt.
老爷子一直没能释怀。
Pops never quite got over that one.
他的小跟班不能跟随他的脚步。
His army brat gimp not being able to follow in his footsteps.
哦，就是父母的爱。
Oh, just a parent's love.
嘿。
Hey.
尼尔公园有炸弹爆炸的报告。
Reports of a bomb going off in Neil Park.
到目前为止，只有一人死亡。
So far, there is only one fatality.
如果有更多信息，我们会及时通知您。
We'll keep you updated as more information becomes available.
我想我今天跑步的时候听到的。
I think I heard that on my run today.
哦,那打击。
Oh, that blows.
那家伙看起来很眼熟。
That dude looks familiar.
呃……不再是了，我的朋友。
Eh... not anymore, my friend.
啊,终于。
Ah, finally.
-给你。-那个老家伙呢?
- Here you go. - Where's the usual guy?
今天不用我操心了，伙计。
Uh, not my day to keep track, bud.
是啊，只要熏牛肉是炸弹就行。
Yeah, well, as long as the pastrami's bomb.
熏牛肉早餐吗?
Pastrami for breakfast?
朋友，没尝过就别挑剔。
Don't knock it till you try it, my friend.
无论如何,老兄。
Whatever, dude.
嗯，这就够了。
Eh, that's good enough.
不用找了。
Here, keep the change.
嘿，圣诞快乐，你这肮脏的动物。
Hey, merry Christmas ya filthy animal.
今天不适合去公园，我猜。
Bad day to go to the park, I guess.
是的。
Yeah.
十磅塑胶炸药。
Ten pounds of semtex.
很可能远程连接了一个中程雷管。
Most likely remotely wired to a medium range detonator.
不管是谁干的，他都想看。
Whoever did this wanted to watch.
我不认为这是偶然的受害者。
I don't think this was a chance victim.
把一个人炸成这样一定很生气。
Gotta be real pissed to blow a guy up like this.
是的,有。
Yeah, there's that.
你觉得这只是单纯的仇杀吗?
You think this was just a simple vendetta?
——不是吗?-我不知道。
- Don't you? - I don't know.
想要看得更清楚，你知道的，看看整个棋盘。
Wanna look beyond the obvious, you know, check the whole board.
好的,鲍比·菲舍尔。
Okay, Bobby Fischer.
让我们去钓鱼。你觉得呢?
Let's go fishing. What do you think?
这是军用级别的扳机。
Well, it's a military-grade trigger.
那是定制工作。花了很多时间在这上面。
That's a custom job. A lot of man hours on this.
我是说，他是个事业有成的人。
I mean, this is a career man.
我想他会从自己的作品中得到刺激。
I think he gets a thrill out of his own handiwork.
我不认为这是最后的结局。
I don't think this is the endgame.
什么……?
What the...?
啊!
Ah!
嘿，疯人院的囚犯们?
Hey, the inmates running the asylum?
替换蛋糕刚到。我们出了点事。
Replacement cake just arrived. We had an incident.
嘿，伙计们，小声点。
Hey, guys, keep it down.
佐伊想提前打开你的礼物，所以我让她了。
Um, Zoey wanted to open your present early, so I let her.
哦。你收到我的短信了吗?
Oh. Did you get my text?
是的，我说了。
Yeah, um, I did.
,嗯…苏伊，你爸打电话找你。
And, uh... Hey, Zoey, your dad's on the phone.
嘿,佐伊熊!
Hey, Zoey bear!
生日快乐,亲爱的。
Happy birthday, honey.
你怎么没来，爸爸?
Why aren't you here, Dad?
亲爱的，我希望我能去。
Well, honey, I wish I could be there.
我得工作。我摆脱不了。
I had to work. I couldn't get out of it.
你总是这么说。这是我的生日。
That's what you always say. It's my birthday.
妈妈说那就是个假期，她来了。
Mom says that's basically a holiday, and she's here.
你知道的，电脑小精灵从不睡觉，苏伊。
Well, you know, computer gremlins never sleep, Zoey.
收到我的礼物了吗?
You get my present?
是的。
Yeah.
你喜欢它吗?
You like it?
不，我喜欢魔术。
No, I love magic.
我练习，但我不确定我是否已经学会了。
I practice, but I'm not sure if I've got it yet.
我觉得你应该从右手开始耍这个把戏，苏伊。
I think you got to start that trick with your right hand, Zoey.
哦。
Oh.
对不起。
Sorry.
就是它，就在那里!你明白了。
That's it, right there! You got it.
是的，我会继续练习的……
Yeah, I'll keep practice...
今晚还有更多的魔术表演吗?
more magic tricks tonight?
我相信我的朋友们会喜欢的。
I'm sure my friends would like it.
你知道吗?我只是碰巧有胡迪尼手铐。
You know what? I just happen to have Houdini handcuffs.
我们今晚可以试试这个把戏。
We could try this trick tonight.
嘿，后面那个白痴是谁?
Hey, who's that idiot in the back?
这是恩佐。
That's Enzo.
向佐伊问好。我们一起工作。
Say hi to Zoey. We work together.
-这是我哥们。-你好啊，苏伊
- This is my buddy. - Well, hey there, Zoey.
我听说你也喜欢魔术。
Hey, I hear you like magic, too.
如果你爸爸一直上班迟到我可能会让他消失。
You know, maybe I'm gonna make your dad disappear if he keeps running late to work all the time.
我是说，这家伙太不专业了。
I mean, this guy is so unprofessional.
是的。我得走了。
Yeah. Well, I gotta go.
再见,亲爱的。
Bye, honey.
我爱你。生日快乐。
I love you. Happy birthday.
我得走了，派对时间到了。
I got to go, party time.
谢谢你抽空见我。
Um, thanks for making the time.
是的。嘿，你小心那些男孩。嗯?
Yeah. Hey, you watch out for those boys. Huh?
我爱你。
I love you.
哦，该死的，兄弟!
Oh, hell no, bro!
拜托，熏牛肉三明治怎么搞砸的?
Come on, how do you fuck up a pastrami sandwich?
你知道吗?不。
You know what? No.
-兰多，我得休息十分钟。很酷?——嗯?
- Lando, I-I gotta take ten. Cool? - Huh?
不，不，拜托，慢慢来，兄弟。
No, no, come on, it's slow, bro.
新来的快递员是逃不掉的。
And the new delivery guy's not getting away with this shit.
另外，我还有几层楼的生意要做，所以…——是吗?新工作前景?-天啊，这是个天使。
Plus, you know, I got a little business a couple floors down, so... - Yeah? New job prospect? - Oh, man, this one's an angel.
——是吗?炎热的金发女郎吗?——没有。不，不，跟上。
- Yeah? The hot blonde? - No. No, no, keep up.
这是艾娃。那是7楼的小妞。
That's Ava. That's the 7th floor chick.
她的……她疯了。她简直疯了。
She's... She's crazy. She's like legit crazy.
脑子疯了，床上也疯了，对吧?
Ah, crazy in the head, crazy in bed, right?
是啊，但这就像煮兔子一样疯狂。
Yeah, but this is like boiling bunny's crazy.
这是一个不同的…不管怎样，帮我个忙。
It's a different... Anyway, just do me favor.
如果她来了，就告诉她我不在。好吧?
If she shows up here, just tell her I'm not here. Okay?
你知道玛丽会查看监控录像吧?
Hey, you do know Mary checks the security feeds, right?
你以为我没想过吗，兄弟?
You don't think I thought of that, bro?
我的办公桌在这间办公室的盲区。
My desk is in the blind spot of this office.
没我看起来那么蠢。
Mm. Not as dumb as I look.
-我不知道，兄弟。——闭嘴。
- I don't know about that, bro. - Shut up.
这该死的家伙。
This fucking guy, man.
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell?
不管发生什么事……坐好别动。
No matter what happens... stay seated.
奥兰多，这是一个无法逃避的问题。
Orlando, this is one problem there is no running from.
这他妈是谁?
Who the hell is this?
你左边最上面的抽屉里，有一面镜子。
Top drawer on your left, there's a mirror.
拿出来。
Take it out.
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
恩佐，我对天发誓，我要揍扁你。
Enzo, I swear to God, I'm going to kick your ass.
再猜,婊子。
Guess again, bitch.
奥兰多，你今天就会死除非你照我说的做。
Orlando, you will die today unless you do exactly as you're told.
所以，拿起镜子，把它放在你的椅子下，然后看。
So take the mirror, place it under your chair, and look.
热。
Hotter.
——热。-哦，上帝啊。
- Hotter. - Oh, Jesus Christ.
——是的。-这是什么鬼?
- Yes. - What the hell is this?
把你的手放在上面。
Put your hand on it.
把你的手放在上面!
Put your hand on it!
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is that?
椅子上的塞姆汀炸药够史上最大的新年表演用了。
There's enough semtex on that chair for the biggest New Year's show in history.
它对压力敏感，所以不会有突然的震动。
It's pressure-sensitive, so no more sudden jolts.
我不知道你有没有注意到椅子周围的新地毯?
Oh, and I don't know if you noticed that new area rug around the chair?
那是一个电栅栏。
That is an electric fence.
因此，如果你试图摆脱，就像你习惯于逃避大多数问题一样，这个问题不会让你走远。
So if you try and roll out, like you're used to running from most of your problems, this one won't let you get far.
你现在注意听我说话了吗，奥兰多?
Do I have your attention now, Orlando?
或者我该叫你红骑士?
Or should I call you Red Knight?
那是你的黑客账号，对吧?
That was your hacker handle, wasn't it?
你因为你的所作所为只受到轻微的惩罚，但我想这是因为你是个叛徒。
You got a slap on the wrist for what you did, but I guess that comes with being a rat.
嘿，听着，如果你是某种黑客爱好者，我很抱歉让你失望了，但我已经退出游戏很长时间了。
Hey, look, if you're some kind of a hacking enthusiast, I'm sorry to disappoint you, but I've been out of the game a long time now.
我觉得你会恢复得很好的。
Oh, I think you'll pick it back up just fine.
如果你觉得这个位置现在很热，那接下来会更热。
If you think that seat is hot now, it's about to get a whole lot hotter.
对我微笑。
Smile for me.
你想从我这里得到什么?
What do you want from me?
两层:
Two floors up:
银行家，对冲基金骗子，混蛋，随便你怎么称呼他们。
bankers, hedge fund crooks, jack-holes, whatever you want to call them.
我要你去抢。
I want you to rob them.
如果我被抓，我要面对20个。
If I get caught, I'm facing 20.
我再也见不到我的家人了。
I'll never see my family again.
嗯，这是看待事物的一种有趣的方式，因为当你被炸飞的时候，你真的再也见不到他们了。
Well, that's a funny way of looking at things, because you'll really never see them again when you're blown to kingdom come.
难道你不想有机会修复你那破婚姻吗?
Don't you want a chance to fix that shit marriage of yours?
没有完成任务，你就会死。
Failure to complete your mission, you die.
如果你的朋友干涉，你就会死。
Your friends interfere, you die.
报警，你就死定了。
Call the police, you die.
你死后，你的妻子和漂亮的小女儿也会死。
And after you die, your wife and pretty little daughter will die, too.
我…我做不到。
I... I can't do this.
哦，别谦虚了。
Oh, don't be modest.
这是你的本性。
This is your nature.
你没有选择。
And you don't have a choice.
如果我这么做，我就能回家吗?
If I do this, I go home?
试一试也无妨。
Never hurts to try.
我研究过他们的系统。
I have researched their system.
当然了。
Of course you did.
他们有封锁保安。
They got blockade security.
如果我闯进去，90秒后系统就会关闭，锁定账户。
If I break in, there's 90 seconds till it shuts down, locks the accounts.
这就是我选择你的原因。
That's why I chose you.
好吧,一件事。我需要我的音乐。好吧?
Okay, one thing. I need my music. Okay?
只要不是国家就行。
As long as it's not country.
这不是国家。
It's not country.
好吧。
All right.
Okay.
我们在。
We're in.
我从未怀疑过你。
I never doubted you.
我担心的不是这个。
That's not the part I was worried about.
嘿，你看到这个了吗?有个漏洞。
Hey, have you seen this? There's been a breach.
现在开始九十秒。看来你被抓了。
Ninety seconds starts now. Looks like you got caught.
-你闯入银行，人们会注意到的。
- You break into banks, people notice.
恩佐在哪儿?
Where's Enzo?
嘿,嘿,嘿。
Hey, hey, hey.
那个混蛋在哪，恩佐?
Where is that asshole, Enzo?
他躲了我一个星期了。
He's been ducking me for a week.
安静,安静。呆在那里。呆在那里。
Quiet, quiet. Stay there. Stay there.
这层楼的人都是混蛋吗?
What, is everyone on this floor a total jerk?
是的,呆。他的座位下面有个炸弹，如果你们谁离开，你们都他妈死定了!
Yes, stay. There's a bomb under his seat, and if either of you leave, you're both fucking dead!
嗯…一个什么?
Uh... A what?
看看我的椅子下面。
Look under my chair.
狗屎!
Shit!
我建议你让他工作趁你还没收拾好自己的烂摊子。
I suggest you let him work before there's too many pieces of you to clean up.
是的，是的，我在处理。
Yeah, yeah, I'm handling it.
该死的。不,不!
Damn it. No, no!
-想办法。我的装备在储物柜里。
- Figure it out. - My gear is in the locker.
我要你把这关了，我好拿我的工具箱。
I need you to shut this down so I can get my kit.
-我得走了-你哪儿也不能去。
- I-I have to go. - You can't go anywhere.
如果你走，我们都会死。
If you leave, we're both dead.
请。我需要你的帮助。
Please. I need your help.
-你叫什么名字?——艾娃。
- What's your name? - Ava.
发生什么事情了?
What's happening?
艾娃，帮我拿一下我的储物柜，好吗?
Ava, I need you to get my locker, okay?
我的工具箱在里面。
My kit's in there.
如果你不这么做，我们就死定了。
If you don't do that, we're dead.
走了。走,走!
Go. Go, go!
——好的。——好着急。
- Okay. - Better hurry.
四分之一，蓝色储物柜。
Fourth over, blue locker.
对，就在那里，就在那里。
Yeah, right there, right there.
- - - - - -来吧。-好吧，密码是什么?
- Come on. - All right, what's the code?
9 - 12…- Nine-12…我需要锁……第三个数字是什么?
It's 9-12... - Nine-12... I need the lock... - What's the third number?
33。
Thirty-three.
那是错误的代码。
That's the wrong code.
36, 9-12-36。百分百。
Thirty-six, 9-12-36. Hundred percent.
代码是什么?
What's the code?
-就是这样，走吧!加油，加油!——有!
- That's it, go! Come on, come on! - Got it!
滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答……
Tick, tock, tick, tock, tick, tock, tick, tock...
三十秒。
Thirty seconds.
在哪里?
Where is it?
就为了这个?
All this for that?
这能让我们活着离开这里。
This is what's gonna get us out of here alive.
这是我做的一个后门程序能让我突破大多数防火墙。
It's a backdoor program I made that allows me to break through most firewalls.
好吧。
All right.
这更好的工作。
This better work.
不。不。
No. No.
来吧。
Come on.
他把我的系统锁在外面了。
He locked me out of my system.
好工作,奥兰多。
Good work, Orlando.
有些人称之为魔法，我称之为擅长工作。
Some people call it magic, I call it being good at my job.
红色警报，全体准备!
Code red, all hands on deck!
很好，你们俩。
Very good, you two.
人类屁股顶着火焰能做出的事真是太神奇了。
It's amazing what humans can do with their asses up against the flame.
告诉我到底是怎么回事。
Tell me what the hell is going on.
你喜欢电影吗，奥兰多?
You like movies, Orlando?
我现在才不管什么电影。
I don't give a shit about movies right now.
我真的很喜欢《现代启示录》。
I really like Apocalypse Now.
我有点像威拉德，顺流而下完成我的任务。
You know, I'm kinda like Willard, floating down the river to complete my mission.
而你，嗯，我…我猜你和我被困在船上了。
And you, well, I... I guess you're stuck on the boat with me.
这是什么?
What is this?
必须以极端的偏见消除外来者。
Outsiders must be eliminated with extreme prejudice.
-我只是来看恩佐的。-不，不，不，别走
- I just came to see Enzo. - No, no, no, don't go.
那我想你最好表现得特别好，好让我改变主意，不杀你。
Oh, then I guess you better be extra good, so I change my mind and don't kill you.
这是一个好女孩。
That's a good girl.
现在去找个地方坐下来欣赏表演吧。
Now go take a seat and enjoy the show.
——这是正确的。-会没事的
- That's right. - It's gonna be okay.
好了，奥兰多，屏幕上的数字。
Now, Orlando, the numbers on your screen.
我要你从你刚黑进那个账户的钱里转两百万。
I want you to transfer $2 million from the funds you just hacked into that account.
这需要时间。
It's gonna take time.
别瞎扯了。你有五分钟时间。
Don't bullshit a bullshitter. You have five minutes.
清楚……当我叫你叫的时候，你唯一的问题应该是，“叫多大声?”
Be clear... When I tell you to bark, your only question should be, "How loud?"
我要准备下一个任务了。
I'm gonna prep our next mission.
河下游见。
See you down the river.
嘿。
Hey.
嘿,艾娃。
Hey, Ava.
有同事发现你不见了吗?
Hey, is there anyone at work that might notice you're missing?
——没有人?——没有。
- No one? - No.
我的老板今天不在。
My-my boss isn't in today.
唯一知道我在这里的人是…不，不，先生，不，不。
The only person that knows I'm here is... No, no, sir, sir. No, no.
我明明说的是熏牛肉，不是腊肠。
I-I clearly said pastrami, not salami.
-我是说，我理解…恩佐,恩佐。
- I-I mean, I understand... - Enzo, Enzo.
那不是我的……耶稣!
That's not my... Jesus!
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
好吧，艾娃，我很抱歉，但你不能这样出现在我的工作现场。
Okay, uh, Ava, I'm really sorry, but you cannot show up to my work like this.
——这是…-他的座位下面有个炸弹。
- This is... - There's a bomb under his seat.
什么?
What?
-她在说什么?-新闻里的公园炸弹客。
- What's she talking about? - Park bomber on the news.
我想这就是他。
I think this is him.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
我要吐了。
I'm gonna be sick.
奥兰多，别让他走。
Orlando, don't let him leave.
-搞什么鬼?!-嘿，恩佐，如果你走，我们都得死。
- What the fuck?! - Hey, Enzo, if you leave, we're all dead.
——耶稣,伙计!-恩佐，听我说。
- Jesus, dude! - Enzo, please, listen.
听?你他妈听到墙里的声音了吗?
Listen? Listen to the fucking voice in the walls?
你他妈今天在这里干什么?
What the fuck are you even doing here today?
你的办公室关门了!
Your-your office is closed!
等等，哇，哇，哇……你是…贱人，你也参与了吗?
Wait-wait, whoa, whoa, whoa... Are you... Bitch, are you part of this?
-我什么?!-你为什么在这里?
- Am I what?! - Why are you here?!
我在找你，你这个混蛋!
Looking for you, you asshole!
嘿,嘿,嘿。
Hey, hey, hey.
我才是有能力帮你的人。
I'm the one who's got the skills to help you.
不是他们。让他们去。
Not them. Let 'em go.
恩佐，别进去。
Hey, Enzo, don't go in there.
对不起,兄弟。我很抱歉。我不能……我做不到。
I'm sorry, bro. I'm sorry. I can't... I can't do it.
我帮你叫警察。好吧?
I'll call the cops for you. Okay?
如果你进去，我们都会死。
If you go in there, we're all dead.
是聪明的。恩佐,不!
Be smart. Enzo, no!
我很抱歉。对不起。
I'm sorry. Sorry.
好吧。
Okay.
艾娃,失望!
Ava, down!
恩佐,不!
Enzo, no!
我就知道!这是军事。
I knew it! It's military.
只是不是现代军队。
Just not modern military.
越南的时代。
Vietnam era.
压力敏感。
Pressure sensitive.
越共曾经使用过。
Viet Cong used to use them.
在扳机上放一根羽毛，试着把它取下来，嘭。
Put so much as a feather weight on the trigger, try and take it off, kaboom.
该死的!就像圣经里说的那样。
Damn! That's like Biblical old.
就像我参加玛士撒拉的成人礼一样。
That's like I was at Methuselah's bar mitzvah old.
这是四个音节，玛士撒拉，哦。
Those are four syllables, Methuselah, ooh.
是啊，我帮他泡妞了。我是第一个帮他泡妞的人。
Yeah, I got him laid. I was the first guy to get him laid.
我敢打赌。
I bet.
-我哥哥从越南回来了。——是吗?
- My big brother came back from 'Nam. - Yeah?
他教了我这些爆炸性的东西，把它变成了我们的爱好。
He kinda taught me all this explosive stuff, made it kind of a hobby for us.
-这就解释了很多。-哦,是的。我们是纵火。
- That explains a lot. - Oh, yeah. We were pyromaniacs.
你炸的够多了，你的电线也会交叉。
You blow enough shit up, your wires will be crossed, too.
好吧。
Okay.
嗯,那又怎样?我们去了每个退伍军人互助小组问他们谁的肩膀上有碎片，还是怎样?
Um, so what? We head to every veteran's support group and ask who's got a chip on their shoulder, or what?
当然，我们可以一边做一边举办烘焙义卖。
Sure, we can host a bake sale while we're at it.
事实上，我觉得你会喜欢搜身那些老兵的。
Actually, I think you might enjoy patting those vets down.
做个体腔检查什么的。
Give a cavity search, whatever.
哦，是的，我喜欢。
Oh, yeah, love it.
不如等鉴证科的指纹出来再说?
Why don't we just wait for a fingerprint from forensics?
所有单位，前往哈德逊塔。
All units, proceed to Hudson Tower.
发生了爆炸。再重复一遍,所有单位。
There's been an explosion. Repeat, all units.
我们有一块奶酪。一定会有披萨的。
We got a piece of cheese. There's gotta be a pizza.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
这首歌献给你的老朋友。
This one goes out to that late buddy of yours.
再见,恩佐。
Bye-bye, Enzo.
恩佐!恩佐!
Enzo! Enzo!
放松。
Easy, now.
艾娃!
Ava!
艾娃，能听到我说话吗?
Ava, can you hear me?
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
为什么?天花板的一部分砸到你的头，你会生气吗?
Why? Would you be after part of the ceiling hit you in the head?
这是一个遗憾。但这也不是第一次有人因为你的罪过而堕落了。
It's a pity. But it wouldn't be the first time others have fallen for your sins.
你杀了他，你个混蛋!他什么也没做!
You killed him, you son of a bitch! He didn't do anything!
哦,请。你认识他吗?
Oh, please. Did you even know him?
还是对你来说，他只是另一个无名的程序?
Or was he just another nameless, faceless program to you?
你也许从没杀过人，奥兰多，但你夺走的生命比我想象的还要多。
You may have never murdered anyone, Orlando, but you have taken more lives than I could ever dream of.
你会为此付出代价的，你个混蛋。
You're gonna pay for this, you son of a bitch.
-你会为此付出代价的我是- - - ?
- You're gonna pay for this. - Am I?
你屁股上绑了足够的C4炸药是第一个登上火星的人。
You're the one with enough C4 strapped to your ass to be the first man on Mars.
对不起，我就是忍不住。
Sorry, I just couldn't resist.
好了，来吧，别废话了。
All right, come on, let's cut the shit.
911事件后，LCPD的反应时间是7分钟。
LCPD response time to something of our nature post-9/11 is seven minutes.
加上圣诞节的流量，最多15辆。
With Christmas traffic, we've got 15 max.
你怎么知道的?
How do you know?
今早公园里的炸弹?
That bomb in the park this morning?
你必须测试这些东西，否则它们可能会……砰!
You gotta test these things out, or they might go... Bang!
你该庆幸是你的老朋友维克多而不是你。
Just be glad it was your old pal Victor and not you.
——维克多?-或者我应该说v -浩劫?
- Victor? - Or should I say V-Havoc?
你们俩以前可是黑帽帮的得力助手。
You two were quite the black hat team back in the day.
你们俩都没有得到应得的惩罚，对吧?
Neither one of you got the sentence you deserved, did you?
虽然他被赦免了罪。
Thought he was absolved from sin.
回到日常生活。
Back to the daily routine.
早上六点慢跑，六点四十五喝咖啡，七点十五在公园看新闻。
Six AM jog, 6:45 coffee, 7:15 news in the park.
我想，我们是有习惯的生物，是福也是祸。
We are creatures of habit, a blessing and a curse, I suppose.
这是什么，仇杀吗?
So what is this, a vendetta?
在你看来，这是份工作。
As far as you're concerned, this is a job.
我花了很长时间研究你的习惯。
A job I've spent a very long time studying your habits for.
你真的应该多待在家里。
You really should spend more time at home.
我猜你希望只要再给你一次机会就能挽救你的婚姻。
I'm guessing you wish you could fix that marriage of yours if you just had one more shot.
二百万美元。
Two million dollars.
你可以去某个小岛上养老。
You can go retire on an island somewhere.
在现在的经济状况下，你不能靠两百万退休。
You can't retire on two million in this economy.
再说了，那钱不是给我的，是给你的。
Besides, that money wasn't for me, that was for you.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
你做了什么?
What have you done?
你赢得了它。
You earned it.
警察会同意的，但我想要更多。
The police would agree, but I want more.
圣堂武士债券?我不明白你的意思。
Templar Bonds? I don't understand.
你刚刚可以进入一家银行。你为什么想要债券?
You-you just had access to a bank. Why would you want bonds?
我才不管什么债券，你个白痴。
I don't give a shit about bonds, you idiot.
我想拥有所有者。
I want to own the owners.
我想让所有的小猪都生活在恐惧中。
I want all the little pigs to live in fear for a change.
我要我的靴子踩在他们的脖子上。
I want my boots on their fucking neck.
我要他们的钱，他们的信息，锁在他们的小保险箱里。
I want their money, I want their information, locked away in their little security deposit boxes.
你想要他们的服务器。
You want their servers.
唯一能找到那些在单独加密的硬盘上有访问密码的盒子。
And the only way to those with access codes on individually encrypted drives in those boxes.
完全难以捉摸的。
Perfectly untraceable.
所有人都在6点安全网络触手可及的范围内，你要在60分钟内锁定之前帮我渗透并驱散这个网络。
All within an arm's reach of a six-point security grid, a grid that you will infiltrate and diffuse for me before it locks in 60 minutes.
-你疯了。-我是个乐观主义者。
- You're crazy. - I'm an optimist.
我需要更多的准备。
I need more prep.
-我需要更多装备。-你浪费的时间越多，特警就越快冲进来，用枪扫射。
- I need more gear. - The more time you waste, the sooner SWAT bursts in, guns blazing.
你觉得他们会先问问题吗?
You think they'll ask questions first?
好吗?
Well?
好吧，我来做。
All right, I'll do it.
好男孩。
Good boy.
你他妈在干什么?
What the fuck are you doing?
我不知道你在说什么。
I don't know what you're talking about.
你把"人质"拼错了。
You spelled "hostage" wrong.
你点击发送，我就杀了佐伊。
You hit send, I kill Zoey.
我只是想让他们知道我没事。
Look, I just wanna let 'em know I'm okay.
你以为我是白痴吗，你个常春藤盟校的混蛋?
You think I'm an idiot, you Ivy League prick?
就当这是事实吧。
Take this as a fact.
我比你聪明。
I am smarter than you.
如果你再出岔子，我就炸了你。
If you deviate again, I'm going to blow your ass up.
在他们尽可能多地收集你之后，你美丽的小佐伊，她会在爸爸的葬礼上哭得泪流满面的。爸爸,爸爸……
And after they've collected as much of you as they can, your beautiful little Zoey, oh, she'll cry her little brown eyes out at Daddy's funeral. Daddy, Daddy...
只有你的棺材会装C4炸药。
Only your casket's gonna be wired with C4.
然后我开车去你父母家，鲁斯和本，在中央大街801号，把他们也杀了。
And then I'll drive to your parents' house, Ruth and Ben, on 801 Center Street and kill them, too.
我需要继续吗?
Do I need to keep going?
我拥有你。
I own you.
说出来。“我拥有你。”
Say it. "I own you."
你拥有我。
You own me.
这是正确的。好。
That's right. Good.
既然我们已经达成一致了，在你打通前五关后，我会帮你拆除炸弹来完成任务。
Now that we're on the same page, after you penetrate the first five levels, I will deactivate the bomb for you to complete the mission.
你知道有多少人会保护这些服务器吗?
Do you have any idea how many people will be guarding these servers?
嘿,奥兰多?用你的聪明才智告诉我，是哪家公司负责圣殿骑士债券的IT业务?
Hey, Orlando? Use that big brain of yours and tell me, what company runs IT for Templar Bonds?
我们
We do.
啊!
Ah!
好吧。
Okay.
我们可以进行有效载荷空投来清除潜伏者。
We could do a payload drop to cut lurkers.
但即使我们通过了前五个安全系统，如果没有人类的安全密码，我们也无法通过最后一个。
But even if we get through the first five parts of the security grid, there's no way to get through the last without clearance codes from a human.
但论坛上说红骑士是个传奇。
But the forums say Red Knight is a legend.
听着，我不管论坛上怎么说。
Look, I don't care what the forums say.
事情就是这样。
It is what it is.
你做你的，我做我的。
You do your part, I will do mine.
那是什么?
What is that?
能让我跑得更快的东西。
Something to help me move a little faster.
好吧。
Okay.
时钟的滴答声。
Clock's ticking.
出来吧，出来吧，不管你在哪里。
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
他们说你恐高。
They say you're afraid of heights.
嗯，它们不是我的最爱。看起来不太大。
Well, they're not my favorite. That doesn't look too big.
专业提示，跳伞就能搞定了。
Hey, pro tip, skydiving will take care of that.
除非飞机着火，否则我是不会跳下去的。
Yeah, I'm not jumping out of a plane unless it's on fire.
哟!
Yo!
坐办公室的人，你们没有权限，在30码外。
Desk jockeys, you don't have clearance, 30-plus yards back.
60码，至少60码。
I'd say 60, at least 60 yards.
这是……那是残骸区。
That's... That's the debris zone.
你现在站的地方，我们称之为蒸汽区。
Where you're standing right now, we call that the vapor zone.
你好吗，托拜厄斯?
How you doin', Tobias?
我的拆弹小组可能都扛不住。
My bomb squad might not carry the weight of twat.
不是你想惹的人，你知道，因为你们就像，滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答……如果你是拆弹小组的人，那就给我吹箫。
Not the guys you want to piss off, you know, 'cause you guys be like, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick... Oh, if you're the bomb squad guys, then blow me.
快他妈进去。我们得到了简报。
Get the fuck in there. We got briefing.
我希望它是简短的。
I hope it's brief.
噢…什么……?
Ow... What...?
艾娃。艾娃,你明白吗?
Ava. Ava, you okay?
发生了什么事?
What happened?
我需要你保持冷静，好吗?
I need you to stay calm, okay?
我得把这里的事做完。
I gotta finish what I'm doing over here.
-怎么了?-是那个女孩她还活着。
- What's going on? - It's the girl. She's alive.
谁在乎啊?专注于手头的任务。
Who gives a shit? Focus on the task at hand.
我得到了丫。
I got ya.
哦。
Uh-oh.
嘿,嗯…嘿，我们这里出了点状况。
Hey, uh... Hey, we got a situation over here.
嘿，混蛋，醒醒。
Hey, asshole, wake up.
你可不能这样跟我说话。
Well, that's no way to talk to me.
我得离开这椅子去拿灭火器。
I need to get out of this chair to get that fire extinguisher.
没有机会。
No chance.
如果洒水装置失灵，一切都会毁了。
If these sprinklers go off, it's gonna crash everything.
太糟糕了。你的电脑死机了，你也死机了。
Too bad. Your computer dies, you die.
嘿,艾娃。
Hey, Ava.
我需要你把火扑灭。
I need you to put out that fire.
你能帮我吗?
Can you do that for me?
希望她的腿没有断。
Let's hope her legs aren't broken.
加油！加油
Come on, come on.
别让洒水器熄火。
Don't let those sprinklers go off.
那就这样吧。
There you go.
好姑娘。
Good girl.
妈的，我喜欢看人类面对压力。
Goddamn, I love watching humans face pressure.
他们会适应吗，还是会像电梯里的小猫咪一样，枯萎枯萎?
Do they adapt, or do they shrivel up and wilt, like that little pussy in the elevator?
你疯狂的混蛋!让我们出去!
You crazy asshole! Let us out!
奥兰多，抓住身后的手铐。
Orlando, grab the handcuffs behind you.
做到!
Do it!
姑娘，去把自己拷在墙上的办公架子上。
Girl, go cuff yourself to one of the office racks on that wall.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
我能相信你吗?
Can I trust you?
是时候反击了。
It's time to fight back.
我要打开这个。
I'm gonna open this one.
给你。
Here you go.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
噢,看。看这多可爱。
Oh, look. Look how cute this is.
嘿,奥兰多。
Hey, Orlando.
——你出名。-我的天啊
- You're famous. -  Oh, my God.
我的上帝。
My God.
最新消息，我们了解到更多关于哈德逊大厦爆炸的信息。
This just in, we're currently learning more information about the Hudson Tower explosion.
目前被认定为恐怖分子♪生日快乐…♪
Currently being treated as an active terrorist... ♪ Happy birthday... ♪
谣传爆炸的幕后主使是奥兰多·弗莱尔。
The man rumored to be behind the explosion is Orlando Friar.
由于他的参与，他面临着相当多的监禁指控。——妈妈。
He faced considerable prison charges - due to his involvement... - Mom.
因为世界科技公司的窃听丑闻而被起诉。
With the World Tech hacking scandal before he turned state's evidence.
我们正在寻找任何与恐怖组织有关的线索。
We're currently searching for any ties to terror organizations.
爸爸为什么上电视?
Why is Dad on TV?
在军队里，他们称之为假旗。
In the military, they call this a false flag.
别盯着真正的凶手。
Get your eyes off the real killer.
你应该感谢我。
You should be thanking me.
现在他们担心的是泰德·卡钦斯基。
Now they're worried about a wildcard Ted Kaczynski up here.
他们不会那么快就派出骑兵。
They won't send in the cavalry as fast.
不客气
You're welcome.
好了，伙计们，这里没有狗屁区域。
All right, guys, no bullshit zone here.
这些都是事实。
These are the facts.
我们的罪犯是奥兰多·弗莱尔。
Our perp is Orlando Friar.
在十楼活动。
Active on the tenth floor.
这混蛋跟这个城市有仇。
This fuck has a bone to pick with the city.
让我们来讨论资产消除。
Let's discuss asset elimination.
-可以这么说。-对，打膝盖的。
- Quite a way to put it. - Yeah, knee slapper.
听着，我已经派了两支消防队在他发现之前干掉他。
Look, I got two fire teams ready to bust his ass before he knows what's up.
我随时都能就位。
I can get in position anytime.
-说出来。-他有家庭吗?
- Just say the words. - Does he got a family?
是的，妻子和孩子在路上。
Yeah, wife and kid en route.
又不是第一个带孩子的神经病。
Wouldn't be the first psycho with kids.
我只是想在他的孩子成为孤儿之前好好考虑一下。
Just want to weigh our options before we orphan his baby.
是啊，你有什么建议?
Oh, yeah, what do you suggest?
嗯，我不知道。
Well, I don't know.
完整的技术扫描。得到一个视觉。
Full tech sweep. Get a visual.
看看我们面对的是什么。
You know, see what we're up against.
我可以站起来，让你知道我透过我的视线看到了什么。
I can get up and let you know what I see through my sights.
该死，防爆小组的傻逼总是想要荣誉，是吧?
Damn, bomb squad cheese dicks always wanting the glory, huh?
典型。这个怎么样?
Typical. How about this?
我们出击，在他再来刺之前杀了他，像个真正的男人。
We strike, kill the fucker before he stings again, like a real man.
嘿，不要什么荣耀。
Hey, no glory shit.
我的意思是，只是x因素，我不知道，也许是一栋楼的电线要爆炸。
I mean, just the x-factor of, I don't know, maybe a building wired to blow up.
废话。
Bullshit.
别废话了，中士。
Cut the shit, Sergeant.
兰斯，把我们的眼睛抬起来。
Lance, get our eye in the sky up.
复制,首席。我到那儿就告诉你。
Copy that, Chief. I'll let you know when I get there.
好吧，在扣动扳机之前我要确认一下接触情况和要求。华莱士，你先来。
All right, I want a confirmation of contact and demands before trigger pull. Wallace, you got first swing.
守住地面，回来报告。
Secure ground level and report back.
哦,谢谢你,长官。
Oh, thanks, Chief.
托比亚斯，我要和大楼管理员联系，好吗?
Tobias, I want contact with the building manager, all right?
——现在!走了。-没问题，女士
- Now! Go. - You got it, ma'am.
谢谢你,朋友。
Thanks, buddy.
为什么要问他家人的事?
Hey, why ask that shit about his family?
-你在乎什么?——我不喜欢。
- Why do you care? - I don't.
除了黑客，他不是个炸弹客。
Other than a hacker, he ain't a bomber.
敌人朝大厅走去。
Hostiles headed toward the lobby.
——好着急。——大便。
- Better hurry. - Shit.
猜猜还有谁来了。
And guess who else just got here.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
喂?奥兰多……
Hello? Orlando...
也是在她生日那天。
On her birthday, too.
今天是我女儿的生日。
It's my daughter's birthday today.
和…如果下一次你也在呢，对吧?
And... what if you're there for the next one, right?
-是的。-再下一个?
- Yeah. - The one after that?
你给我从椅子上起来。
You get your ass up off that chair.
打个比方。
Figuratively.
带我们离开这鬼地方。
Get us the hell out of here.
好吧。
All right.
我们还没有收到任何关于奥兰多·弗莱尔的消息，那个藏在里面的人。
We've yet to receive any more information on Orlando Friar, the man holed up inside.
然而，我们被告知，当局正在逮捕他的家人，希望建立联系。
However, we are being told that authorities are bringing down his family in hopes to establish communication.
这里有很多窗户，是吧?
Lots of windows up here, huh?
看一看。
Take a look.
不妨挥挥手。
Might as well wave.
到目前为止，战术规程上至少有三名训练有素的射手正盯着你。
By now, tactical protocols will have at least three trained shooters right on you.
你感觉到了吗?
Do you feel it?
我已就位，准备就绪。
I'm in position, locked and loaded.
目标在视线内。
Target is in sight.
好像只是坐在电脑前。
Seems to just be sitting at his computer.
哈。我们处在这么敏感的年龄，你很幸运。
Heh. You are lucky we're in such a sensitive age.
他们可不想在电视直播中爆了你的头。
They don't want to blow your brains out on live TV.
看来我们的游戏进入了下一个阶段，因为现在他们终于认真对待我们了。
Well, it seems that we've reached the next phase of our game, because now they're finally taking us seriously.
是时候坦白了。
Time for the confession.
录制一段视频，读取准确的信息，并将其传播到全世界。
Record a video reading that exact message and stream it to the world.
我想先和我的家人谈谈。
I want to talk to my family first.
-不可能。-你想让我读这个?
- Not a chance. - You want me to read this?
我先和我的家人谈谈。
I talk to my family first.
——或者什么?-不然我不干了。
- Or what? - Or I'm done.
你真是个混蛋，但你确实关心你女儿。
You know, you are a real piece of shit, but you do care about your daughter.
我尊重这一点。
I respect that.
哦,什么?我们现在是朋友吗?
Oh, what? We're buddies now?
让我猜猜，你有恋父情结吗?
Let me guess, you got some kind of a daddy issue?
我和我父亲的关系…复杂。
My relationship with my father is... complicated.
当他不忙着喝酒和揍我的时候，我们在成长过程中确实有点园艺天赋。
When he wasn't busy drinking and kicking my ass, we did have a bit of a green thumb growing up.
你看，种植土壤，是个藏炸弹的好地方。
You see, planter soil, it's a great place to hide a bomb.
24小时不间断的新闻最棒的地方在于，坏人还是可以看的。
And the best part about 24/7 news is that the bad guys get to watch it all the same.
所以他们在这种情况下做的第一件事就是扫视这片区域，但是肥料炸弹，埋在几英尺深的土壤下是不会被发现的。
So the first thing they do in our situation is sweep the area, but a fertilizer bomb, that doesn't show up when it's under a few feet of soil.
你现在就把供词读出来，不然我就按下红色小按钮把你的家人变成汤。
So you read that confession now, or I press my little red button and turn your family into soup.
好了，够了，够了。
All right, enough, enough.
你想让我读这个吗?
You want me to read this?
是的，那太好了。
Yes, that would be great.
奥兰多，我们来点轻松的即兴表演吧。
Oh, and Orlando, let's take it light on the improv.
我是一个非常严格遵守诺言的人。
I'm a real stickler for my words.
有人告诉我，我们接到了来自哈德逊大厦的电话。
I'm being told that we're getting a call from within Hudson Tower.
有可能有人被困在大楼里。
It could possibly be that there is someone trapped inside the building.
打电话的人，你叫什么名字?
Caller, what is your name?
这是住十楼的那个人。
This is the man on the tenth floor.
我要你把我马上发给你的这段视频直播下去。
I want you to go live with this feed I'm about to send you.
嘿,佐伊。
Hey, Zoey.
我的搭档，杰克逊警官，他想问你几个问题。这里有点闷。
My partner, Officer Jackson here, he wants to ask you a few questions. It's kind of stuffy in here.
你为什么不出去呼吸点新鲜空气，吃点零食?
Why don't you go out and get some fresh air, maybe a snack?
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
-你感觉怎么样?——没关系。你可以走了。
- What do you feel like? - It's okay. You can go.
是吗?
Yeah?
-没有不重要的工作，英雄。-连当保姆都不行。
- No job too small, hero. - Not even babysitting.
夫人……警长想和你谈谈。
Ma'am... Chief wants to talk to you.
弗莱尔女士，我需要知道你丈夫的一切，如果他能做出这种事。
Ms. Friar, I need to know everything about your husband, and if he's capable of doing something like this.
不，这里不是奥兰多。
No, this isn't Orlando.
他有案底。
Well, he has record.
我知道他的记录，好吗?
Yeah, I'm aware of his record, okay?
是的，他有一些问题，但他试图改变，他非常努力地扭转局面。
And yes, he has some red marks, but he's tried to change, and he's worked really hard to turn things around.
他的尝试。
He's trying.
所以他在成为证人之前就会被起诉吗?
So he was going to be prosecuted before he turned witness?
嗯,是的。
Um, yeah.
这是,嗯……我在计划…给他一个…但这里不是奥兰多。
It was, um... I was planning, um... on giving him a... But this isn't Orlando.
——我知道。-你怎么知道?
- I know. - How do you know?
因为奥兰多犯了一些非常愚蠢的错误，但他不会冒险失去佐伊。
Because Orlando has made some really stupid mistakes, but the one thing he wouldn't risk losing is Zoey.
看，这对我很有效。
See, that works for me.
不符合这种工作的特征。
Doesn't fit the profile of a gig like this.
我们根据现有的情报。
We're going off present intel.
我给他打电话，他也想给我打电话。
I called and he tried to call me.
我错过了。
Um, I missed it.
队长，你得看看这个。
Chief, you gotta look at this here.
头了。
Heads up.
我叫奥兰多·弗莱尔。
My name is Orlando Friar.
我是对公园和哈德逊大厦爆炸案负责的人。
I am the person responsible for the bombing in the park and Hudson Towers.
大楼里还有更多的炸弹，藏在全城各处。
There are more bombs in the building and hidden throughout the city.
任何不速之客的闯入都会导致数百人死亡。
Any more intrusions from unwanted guests will result in hundreds of deaths.
我希望我讲清楚了。
I hope I am clear.
我骗了你们所有人，骗了我妻子金，骗了我女儿佐伊。
I have lied to all of you, to my wife, Kim, to my daughter, Zoey.
我协助策划了我们历史上最严重的一次金融诈骗。
I helped orchestrate one of the worst financial deceptions in public trust in our history.
首先，我想定下一些基本规则。
First, I want to set some ground rules.
我已准备好赴死。
I am prepared to die.
我被一个死人的开关钩住了。
I am hooked to a dead man's switch.
如果你杀了我，就会引爆所有炸弹…这将是一个血腥的圣诞节
If you kill me, it will trigger all bombs... and it will be a bloody Christmas.
金,佐伊……我爱你!
Kim, Zoey... I love you!
我很抱歉……
I'm sorry...
这里不是奥兰多。他是吓坏了。
This is not Orlando. He is terrified.
-让所有炸弹技术人员准备突破。- - - - - -。
- Get every single bomb tech ready to breach. - On it.
好了，特警，准备袭击。
All right, SWAT, prep for assault.
-等待…——走吧。
- Wait... - Let's go.
拜托，听我说。
Please, just listen to me.
你到底在想什么?
What the hell were you thinking?
你想让你的家人死吗?
Do you want your family to die?
我告诉过你要仔细阅读那一页的内容!
I told you to read exactly what was on that page!
一个准备引爆自己的人是不会动摇的。
A man ready to blow himself up doesn't waver.
那你打算怎么做?
And what are you gonna do about it?
你觉得有办法逃出去吗，混蛋!
Oh, you think there's a way out of this, motherfucker?!
你以为我不会再追杀你和你的小家庭了吗?
You think I won't hunt you and your shitty little family down again?
时钟的滴答声。
Clock's ticking.
你们在说什么?
What were you talking about?
两年前，奥兰多，他和一个…在纽约开了一家大公司
Two years ago, uh, Orlando, he signed on with a... with a big bucks New York startup.
好吧?他们支付了我们所有的账单，这比奥兰多以前的黑客生活好多了。
Okay? And they paid all of our bills, and it was better than Orlando's former life in hacking.
投资银行家，退休老人。
Investment bankers, old retirees.
任何有投资组合的人都受到欢迎。
Anyone with portfolios was welcome.
旧的钱，纽约的钱。
Old money, New York money.
这一切都应该受到法律的规范。
It was all supposed to be regulated, by the books.
但我们很快就意识到为什么他们如此渴望奥兰多。
But we soon realized why they wanted Orlando so badly.
他们利用我黑进手机，黑进服务器。
They used me to crack into phones, to break into servers.
任何事情都可以获得优势。
Anything to gain an edge.
我以为对他们来说只是数据挖掘。
I thought it was just data mining for them.
但事实证明，他们侵入了人们的储蓄……401 ks。
But it turns out they were hacking into people's savings... their 401ks.
你不知道吗?
And you didn't know?
我,嗯…
I, uh...
我任性地天真。
I was willfully naive.
我是说，他们都是有权势的人。
I mean, these were powerful people.
你知道，华尔街的政客们。
You know, Wall Street, politicians.
一旦联邦调查局介入，我就不能再让他们抢劫了。
Once the Feds got involved, I couldn't outright let them rob anyone anymore.
那……买股票的人呢?
And what about... The people who bought in?
破产了，被他们信任的体制吞噬了。
Broke, and eaten by the system they trusted.
不仅仅是有钱的投资者，还有普通人。
And it wasn't just rich investors, it was regular people.
他们的未来，他们的养老金，都没了。
Their futures, their pensions, just gone.
我为那些偷钱和花钱一样快的骗子工作。
I worked for crooks who spent it as fast as they stole it.
没有什么可以回馈的。
There was nothing to give back.
没办法让这些人重获新生。
No way to give these people their lives back.
我们把老板抓起来了。
We put the bosses away.
我和我的搭档达成了协议。
And me and my partner took a deal.
我接受了一个协议。
I took a deal.
你这么做是为了你的家人。
You did what you had to for your family.
当他发现他们在做什么的时候，他就把他们告发了。
When he found out what they were doing, he turned them in.
他没有想到他自己，也没有想到他即将失去的家人。
He didn't think about himself or the family he was about to lose.
我们离开了城市，搬到了这里。
And we left the city and we moved here.
他骗了我，但他最后做了正确的事。
He lied to me, but, um, he did the right thing in the end.
他是个好人。
He's a good man.
他是。
He is.
上膛，上膛。
Locked and loaded, Chief.
绿色的光。
Green light.
绿灯吗?发生了什么?
Green light? What is happening?
好了，你得出去，拜托了。
All right, you need to go outside, please.
-请不要伤害我丈夫。-听着，这不是我们能决定的
- Please don't hurt my husband. - Listen, it's not up to us.
这取决于他。他要么现在结束这一切，要么我们替他结束。
It's up to him. He can either end this now or we'll end it for him.
谁能把她弄出去?
Can somebody get her outside?
——妈妈。——佐伊。
- Mom. - Zoey.
你告诉他们爸爸给我们的留言了吗?
Did you tell them about the message that Dad left us?
是的…是的，他打了电话，还留了言，听起来好像有人在后台。
Yeah... yes, he-he-he called and he left a message, and, um, it sounds like there's someone in the background.
只是听。
Just listen.
嘿，嘿，大家小声点，好吗?
Hey, hey, everyone, keep it down, will you?
嘿，奥兰多，你很有名。
Hey, Orlando, you're famous.
-我的天啊-我听到了。
- Oh, my God. - I hear him.
我听说有人在那里跟他说话。
I hear there's somebody there talking to him.
好吧，我们会考虑的。
All right, we'll take it into consideration.
-你会帮我爸爸吗?-是的，我们会尽力的。在这里。
- Will you help my dad? - Yeah, we'll do our best. Here.
我试着联系大楼经理，埃德蒙·哈里斯。
I tried to reach the building manager, Edmond Harris.
没有人知道他在哪里。甚至他的家人。
No one knows where he is. Even his family.
可能是炸弹客。
Could be the bomber.
局长，我们得在今天有人死之前干掉这混蛋。
Chief, we gotta take this fucker before anybody else dies today.
他说他有个死人的开关随时会爆炸。
He says he's got a dead man's switch ready to blow.
如果我们杀了他，谁知道还会死多少人?
If we kill him, who knows how many more could die?
我们刚才在电话里听到的那个声音，可能是他在发号施令。
That voice we just heard on the phone, he could be calling the shots.
你想试试吗?
You want to take that chance?
你觉得奥兰多是替罪羊吗?
Now do you think maybe Orlando's the patsy?
队长，你看了情况报告。这他妈是虚张声势!
Chief, you read the sitrep. It's a fucking bluff!
我们不会坐在这里听这些年迈的，过气的拆弹小组的人说他们还没有从他们该死的过去中恢复过来。
We're not gonna sit here and listen to these old, washed up bomb squad guys that haven't recovered from their fucked up past.
嘿，这不公平。杰克逊还没老，也没完蛋。
Hey, that's not fair. Jackson's not old and washed up.
好了，给我闭嘴。
Okay, shut the fuck up.
96年圣诞节，第一个电话，家庭纠纷。
Christmas '96, first call, domestic disturbance.
那家伙说如果我们采取行动，他会把房子和孩子都炸了。
Guy said that if we made a move, he'd blow the house, kids at all.
你知道有多少次我会说那个白痴在虚张声势吗?
Do you know how many times I would have said that idiot was bluffing?
我错了多少次?
How many times I was wrong?
这不是你说了算的。
It's not your call.
它不是你的。
And it's not yours.
它是我的。
It's mine.
女王是棋盘上最有价值的玩家。
The queen's the most valuable player on the board.
核实一下事实。下一步怎么办，长官?
Just check the facts. What's the next move, Chief?
好了，我穿过了第四堵墙。
Okay, I'm through the fourth wall.
——屎!——屎?
- Shit! - Shit?
这是高级加密。
It's high-level encryption.
有多高?
How high?
如果五角大楼是10，那就是12.5。
Well, if the Pentagon is a ten, it's a 12.5.
你能打开它吗?
Can-can you crack it?
我没有选择。
I ain't got no choice.
持有。
Holding.
你的命令。
By your command.
红灯，红灯，停下。
Red light, red light, stand down.
罗杰。
Roger that.
别太得意了，华莱士，该你上场了。
Don't get too comfortable, Wallace, you're up to bat.
好。
Good.
不，不，别等我。
No, no, don't wait up.
工作到很晚，参加盛大的宴会，你等着瞧吧。
Working late, big shindig, you'll see.
在我回来之前确保送牛奶的人走了。
Make sure the milkman's gone before I get back.
祝你圣诞快乐。
I wish you a Merry Christmas.
祝你圣诞快乐，新年快乐。
I wish you a Merry Christmas and Happy New Year.
后来,孩子。
Later, baby.
你给你老婆唱圣诞歌?
You sing Christmas songs to your wife?
哦，是的，她在这方面有点怪癖。
Oh, yeah, she's kinky that way.
大家都说，找工作前打个电话是不吉利的。
You know what they say, calling before a job is bad luck.
谁说的?
Who says?
看电影。
The movies.
是啊，他给他老婆打电话，然后他就完蛋了。
Yeah, guy calls his old lady, next thing you know, it's curtains for that guy.
作为一个炸弹制造者，你享受每一刻。
As a bomb guy, you savor every moment.
-有需要联系的人吗?——不。
- You got anyone you need to call? - Nah.
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell was that?
协议。他们在开火前切断了电源。
Protocol. They cut power before they burst in firing.
完成这项工作。
Finish the job.
哦,不……我在5号锁失去了进展。
Oh, no... I lost progress on lock five.
——修复它!-拜托，奥兰多。
- Fix it! - Come on, Orlando.
来吧，你能行的。来吧。
Come on, you got this. Come on.
嘘。让我想想，让我想想。
Shh. Let me think, let me think.
这屋子里没有什么东西能打破它。
There's nothing in this room strong enough to break it.
自己想办法，好吗?自己想办法吧。
Just figure it out, okay? Just figure it out.
肯定有什么黑客的东西你知道你可以用…来吧!任务胜利在望!
There-there has to be some hacker shit that you know that you can use... Come on! Mission victory is in sight!
-生死攸关!你选择!——嘿!
- Life or death! You choose! -  Hey!
你跟我一样完蛋了!
You're as screwed as I am!
如果你能自己闯进来，你会的。
If you could break in here yourself, you would.
想办法吧!
Just figure it out!
好吧。停，停，停，停……-快弄清楚!- - - - - -闭嘴!等等!
Okay. Stop, stop, stop, stop... - Figure it out already! - Shut up! Hold on!
我们得把它淹没。
We got to flood it.
看起来像是标准的DDoS攻击。
It'll look like a standard DDoS attack.
我们借由防御回应。
We backdoor the defense response.
我们淹没服务器。
We flood the servers.
圣堂武士邦德的守卫规程根本没用。
Templar Bonds guard protocols won't stand a chance.
外面的一切都在网络上运行。
Everything out there is running on a network.
所有信号都发送到那个网络。
All sending signals to that network.
如果我能重定向信号，我们就能把它们都送到这里。
If I could redirect the signals, we could send them all here.
我可以利用这些流量让他们的服务器过载，造成瘫痪。
I could use the traffic to overload their servers and jam them up.
这将禁用锁5。
This disables lock five.
唯一的问题是，我们也会堵车。
The only problem is, traffic's gonna hit us, too.
我需要一个盾牌。
I need a shield.
十楼。
Tenth floor.
我发誓，如果我们活捉这家伙，我一定揍他一顿。
I swear, if we take this guy alive, I'm gonna kick his ass.
来吧，老黄狗。
Come on, Old Yeller.
还没到吃草的时候。
It ain't time for pasture yet.
——你明白吗?-是的。
- You okay? - Yeah.
是啊，你妈妈之前把我累坏了。
Yeah, your mom wore me out earlier.
我妈妈不喜欢老男人。另外,她是种族主义。
My mom don't like older men. Plus, she's racist.
我们快到门口了。
We're approaching the door.
嘿，等等，等等。
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
还有其他人在里面。
There's somebody else in there.
——人质吗?——是的,也许吧。
- A hostage? - Yeah, maybe.
这是纤维。
It's fiber time.
哇。不错的平台。
Whoa. Nice rig.
你是说这是一个假释的白领黑客干的?
You're telling me a white collar hacker on parole made that?
很高科技。
Pretty high tech.
华莱士，停下，向后平移。
Wallace, stop, pan back.
锅回来。
Pan back.
我们有个人质。
We got a hostage.
你他妈在干什么?
What the fuck are you doing?
红骑士必须保护女王。
Red Knight has to shield the Queen.
如果我发动攻击，我们就在攻击区。
If I unleash this attack, we're right in the strike zone.
好吧，来吧，快点。应该不会花这么长时间。
All right, well, come on, hurry up. It shouldn't be taking this long.
首席。
Chief.
-怎么了，中士?-有发现了。
- What is it, Sergeant? - We got something.
我们的突击小队在大本营。
Our assault team is at base camp.
我们知道奥兰多在十楼工作。
We know Orlando works on the tenth floor.
我们又发现了一个热信号。
Well, we're picking up another heat signature.
那是哪儿?
Where is that?
就在其中一个服务器机房里。
It's inside one of those server rooms.
他们可能藏在那里。
They're probably hiding in there.
希望他们能融入服务器的热度中。
You know, hoping they would blend in with the heat of the servers.
这个混蛋可能是同伙，也可能是控制他的人。
This jackass could be an accomplice, or someone controlling him.
你一定要抓住这个混蛋。
You gotta get this fucker.
华莱士,停止。
Wallace, stop.
大楼里可能有第二名嫌疑人。
We got a possible second suspect in the building.
可能是失踪的人，埃德蒙·哈里斯。
It could be our missing person, Edmond Harris.
你骗我。
You're shitting me.
-另一个声音。-是的。
- A second voice. - Yeah.
我们很确定其他炸弹可能就在那里。
We're fairly certain that's where the other bombs could be located.
不要告诉我。四楼,对吧?
Don't tell me. Fourth floor, right?
服务器的房间。为什么?
Server room. Why?
那是建筑结构中最薄弱的部分。
Well, that's the weakest part in the building structure.
可能会让整件事都垮掉。
It could bring the whole thing down from there.
好了，特警已经在路上了。
All right, SWAT's en route.
我们需要你们中的一个去见他们。
We need one of you to meet them.
好吧，我这就去。
All right, I'm on it.
不，你待在这里。
No, you stay here.
解除炸弹。我会处理的。
Disarm that bomb. I'll take care of it.
不是一个机会。拜托，电影，伙计。
Not a chance. Come on, movies, man.
他们现在分开了，其中一个要完蛋了。
Guys split up now, it's curtains for one of them.
听着，老黄狗，你撑不下去的。
Listen, Old Yeller, you're never gonna make it.
处理好这个，我来处理那个。
Take care of this, I'll handle that.
就像下棋一样，伙计。
It's like chess, man.
这不是情感。我得到这个。
It's not emotional. I got this.
好吧。听着，行动杰克逊，只要闻到一点霉味，你就得离开。
All right. Well, listen, Action Jackson, you even get a whiff of anything rotten, you bail.
-你听到了吗?——罗杰。
- You hear me? - Roger.
我和你还有未竟的心愿。
Me and you got unfinished business.
——点击瓣。——祝你好运。
- Click clack. - Good luck.
-我就是为这个而生的。-是的。
- I was born for this shit. - Yeah.
奥兰多，把摄像头连上。
Orlando, get the cameras online.
他被困在里面了?
He's trapped in there?
华莱士，我们找到他了。
Wallace, we got him.
嘿，慢点，孩子，慢点。
Hey, slow down, kid, slow down.
看下一步。
See the next move.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
让服务器满屏，完成任务。
Flood the servers, finish the job.
嘿，混蛋，你猜怎么着?
Hey, asshole, guess what?
特警就要来敲你的门了。
SWAT's about to knock on your door.
什么?
What?
走，走，走，走，走，走!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
嘿，嘿，嘿，告诉我最新情况。状态是什么?
Hey, hey, hey, give me an update. What's the status?
来吧。跟我说话。
Come on. Talk to me.
不许动，混蛋!
Don't you move, asshole!
我要去监狱看你。
I'm gonna visit you in prison.
我希望你喜欢当监狱里的婊子，因为你现在正处于水深火热之中。
I hope you like being someone's prison bitch, 'cause you're in the hot seat now.
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is that?
我不是骗子。
I am not a crook.
资本主义猪去死!
Death to the capitalist pig!
是埃德蒙·哈里斯，失踪的人。
It's Edmund Harris, our missing person.
我联系过大楼管理员，埃德蒙·哈里斯，没人知道他在哪。甚至他的家人。
I tried to reach the building manager, Edmund Harris, no one knows where he is. Even his family.
是…?
Is that...?
他死了,华莱士。
He's dead, Wallace.
他的眼睛不见了。
His eye is missing.
我不是骗子。
I am not a crook.
让资本主义的猪去死。
Death to the capitalist pig.
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is that?
这是一个炸弹!每个人都出去!
It's a bomb! Everybody get out!
给我看看里面。有人能读懂我的话吗?
Give me eyes in there. Can anyone read me?
——操。——该死的!
- Fuck. - Damnit!
他妈的。
Fuck.
杰克逊，你没事吧?
Jackson, you all right?
杰克逊,杰克……哦,他妈的。
Jackson, Jack... Oh, fuck.
他妈的我。
Fuck me.
有人能读懂我的话吗?
Can anyone read me?
有人知道吗?该死的!
Anyone? Damnit!
大便。
Shit.
你能告诉我发生了什么事吗?
Can you tell me what happened?
嘿!
Hey!
他还活着吗?
Is he alive?
不要忽略我!他还活着吗?
Don't ignore me! Is he alive?
艾娃,你没事吧?
Ava, you good?
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell was that?
我想他们找到他了。
I think they found him.
哦，他们找到了一些东西。
Oh, they found something, all right.
从现在开始就不会有什么问题了。
It won't be much of a problem from here on out.
为了一份简单的工作要牺牲多少人?
How many must die for a simple job?
你要毁灭多少人，红骑士?
How many lives are you going to destroy, Red Knight?
去你的，你个混蛋!
Fuck you, you cocksucker!
不是我的错，你个狗娘养的!
It's not my fault, you son of a bitch!
在你那毫无价值的生命中承担一次责任吧，你这个可悲的小矮子。
Oh, take responsibility for once in your worthless life, you pathetic little man.
话说回来，语言真是丰富多彩。
Really colorful language back there, though.
我特别喜欢"监狱贱人"这个词
You know, I-I particularly liked "prison bitch."
现在谁是贱人?
Well, who's the bitch now?
哦，那不是反问句。
Oh, that wasn't a rhetorical question.
嘿!现在谁是婊子?
Hey! Who's the bitch now?
我是婊子。
I'm the bitch.
没有更多的游戏。你不可能赢。
No more games. You can't win.
发动他妈的罢工。
Launch the fucking strike.
你想让我开枪吗?
Do you want me to take the shot?
你想让我发动攻击，那就准备好了。
You want me to launch this attack, it's ready.
不，那不是他。他在和别人说话。
No, that is not him. He's talking to somebody.
但我要的是承诺。
But I want promises.
这次我要你答应我。
I want promises this time.
你解除炸弹，然后放了我。
You deactivate the bomb, and you set me free.
我保证。
I promise.
万福马利亚。
Hail Mary time.
长竿。
Officer Reed.
我不建议这样做。
I wouldn't recommend doing that.
快走，不然我就把你变成猫粮，就像你四楼的朋友一样。
Leave now before I turn you into cat food, like your friends on the fourth floor.
你远离。
You stay out.
帮助我。
Help me.
完成任务，士兵!
Finish the job, soldier!
黄色的光。等待下一个线索。
Yellow light. Waiting next cue.
绿色的光。
Green light.
罗杰。绿色的光。
Roger that. Green light.
所有单位，所有单位，撤退。
All units, all units, stand down.
奥兰多不是爆炸者。重复一遍，奥兰多不是炸弹客。
Orlando is not the bomber. I repeat, Orlando is not the bomber.
红灯，红灯!下台!
Red light, red light! Stand down!
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
这是一个失误，感谢上帝。
That's a miss. Thank God.
他肯定在这里和那个房间都有实时信号。
He must have a live feed here and into the rigged room.
他在附近。
He's close by.
我们没有发出更多的热信号。
We aren't making any more heat signatures out.
他在这里。
He's here.
我进来时他看见了我。从标签上读出我的名字。
He saw me as I came in. Read my name right off the tag.
另外，DDoS攻击后整个城市的信号都被干扰了。
Plus, signals are jammed all throughout around the city after that DDoS attack.
唯一能看到这里的方式，现在，就是在这里。
Only way to see in here, right now, is to be here.
士兵,你看到吗?
You see, soldier?
我不是敌人。
I'm not the enemy.
其他人都想杀了你。
Everyone else is trying to kill you.
结束了。
It's finished.
我打破了它。
I broke it.
我从没怀疑过你。
I never doubted you for a second.
最后一个锁是手动操作的。
The last lock is manually operated.
解除所有炸弹，让我走。
Disarm all the bombs and let me go.
伙计，你是个野兽黑客，但你太容易上当了。
Man, you are a beast hacker, but you're gullible as shit.
那里没有化肥炸弹。
There's no fertilizer bomb out there.
没有足够的土壤。我该把它放在哪里呢?
There's not enough soil. Where would I put it?
不，只剩一个炸弹了，奥兰多，就在你下面。
Nah, there's only one bomb left, Orlando, and it's under you.
我完成了我的工作。让我走。
I did my job. Let me go.
我不这么想。
I don't think so.
我将亲自处理最后一把锁。
I'll handle the last lock myself.
哦,不是吗?
Oh, no?
嘿…艾娃。
Hey... Ava.
那盾不是他一个人的。
That shield wasn't just for him.
对我们来说也是如此。
It was for us, too.
他看不到我们，也听不到我们。
He can't see us or hear us.
除非我希望他这么做。
Not unless I want him to.
安静地坐着,奥兰多。
Stay seated, Orlando.
我告诉你什么时候可以安全起床。
I'll let you know when it's safe to get up.
救命啊!
Please help!
他切断了摄像机!那个疯子看不见。
He cut the cameras! That psycho can't see.
好的，小姐。
Okeydoke, miss.
马上把你弄出去。
Get you out of here in a jiffy.
坚持住，红骑士。差不多完成了。
Hang in there, Red Knight. It's almost done.
狗娘养……好了，快离开这里，走吧。
Son of a... Okay, get the hell out of here, go.
-我…——跑
- I-I... - Run.
艾娃,走吧!-艾娃，你出局了
- Ava, go! - Ava, you're out.
——走吧!——帮助他。
- Go! - Help him.
——华莱士。——奥兰多。
- Wallace. - Orlando.
-是的。-你能把我弄出去吗?
- Yeah. - Can you get me out of this thing?
——为什么?你有急事吗?-有一点。
- Why? You in some kind of hurry? - A little bit.
你有多重?我有多重?
- How much do you weigh? - How much do I weigh?
-是的。-嗯,175。
- Yeah. - Uh, 175.
175加1还是177?因为它很重要。
One-seventy-five solid or 177? 'Cause it matters.
据我所知，我已经175岁了。
Last time I checked, I was 175.
什么是生酮饮食?
What is it, keto diet?
把我弄出去，我带你去吃冰淇淋。
Get me outta this thing, I'll take you for ice cream.
是的。全脂,好吗?
Yeah. Full-fat, okay?
啊,该死的。该死的!
Ah, damnit. Damn!
——什么?什么,什么?——屎!
- What? What, what? - Shit!
我阻止不了。
I can't stop it.
它只会爆炸。
It's only rigged to explode.
这是个压力开关。
It's a pressure switch.
让我们看看我能做什么。
Let's see what I can do.
啊，没有出路了。
Ah, there's no way out.
没有出路。
No way out.
你听到了吗，你个混蛋?
Hey, you hear me, you son of a bitch?
我们说好了的。
We made a deal.
我帮你，你放我走。
I help you, you let me go.
我说谎了。
I lied.
你不要脸的……
You motherfucking...
你不该那么做的，混蛋。
You shouldn't have done that, asshole.
-告诉我的家人我爱他们，好吗?-是的。
- Tell my family I love them, okay? - Yeah.
-我知道我们要做什么。-你在想什么?
- I know what we're gonna do. - What are you thinkin'?
安全离开这里。
Get out of here safe.
走了。
Go.
快跑!走吧!
Run! Go!
状态!
Status!
告诉我他妈的状态!
Give me a fucking status!
你这个狗娘养的!
You son of a bitch!
是啊!他还活着!
Yeah! He's alive!
你聪明的混蛋。
You clever motherfucker.
——爸爸的好吗?-是的，爸爸很好。
- Dad's okay? - Yes, Dad is fine.
我待会再回答你的问题，好吗?
Look, I'll answer questions later, all right?
我只想见到我的家人。
I just wanna see my family.
这是电梯里的那个人吗?
Is this the man in the elevator?
是的，那是我的同事。
Yeah, that's my co-worker.
和我的朋友。
And my friend.
他是个好人。
He was a good man.
我害死了他。
And I got him killed.
-我们现在可以见爸爸了，对吧?——是的,亲爱的。
- We can see Dad now, right? - Yes, sweetie.
-他没有遇到麻烦吧?-不，我不这么认为。
- He's not in trouble, is he? - No, I don't think so.
——太太修士。——是的。
- Mrs. Friar. - Yes.
请跟我来，我要带你去见你丈夫。
Come with me, please, I'm gonna take you to see your husband.
“查理不冲浪。”
"Charlie don't surf."
查理……那是哪儿来的来着?
Charlie... Where is that from again?
《现代启示录》。漏洞百出的电影。
Apocalypse Now. Trippy movie.
照片里的人穿着《现代启示录》的衬衫。
The guy in the picture was wearing an Apocalypse Now shirt.
《现代启示录》。
Apocalypse Now.
你喜欢电影吗，奥兰多?
You like movies, Orlando?
我现在才不管什么电影。
I don't give a shit about movies right now.
我真的很喜欢《现代启示录》。
I really like Apocalypse Now.
这是电梯里的那个人吗?
Is this the man in the elevator?
我17岁的时候在建筑工地摔了一跤。
It was a construction gig fall when I was 17.
老爷子一直没能释怀。
Pops never quite got over that one.
他的小跟班不能跟随他的脚步。
His army brat gimp not being able to follow in his footsteps.
哦，父母的爱。
Oh, a parent's love.
“查理不冲浪。”
"Charlie don't surf."
我的办公桌在这间办公室的盲区。
My desk is in the blind spot in this office.
这是他。
It's him.
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell?
艾娃。
Ava.
你在这栋楼的什么地方工作?是圣殿武士债券吗?
Where did you work in this building? Is it Templar Bonds?
不，我在管理办公室工作。为什么?
No, I-I work in the management office. Why?
-所以你有安全通道?-是的。
- So you have security access? - Yeah.
那个金发美女?
Yeah, the hot blonde?
不,不,不。跟上，那是艾娃。那是七楼。
No, no, no. Keep up, that's Ava. That's the seventh floor.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
这是电梯的标准配备吗?
Is that standard in elevators?
我不知道。
I don't know.
嘿，我想我认识你。
Hey, I think I know you.
是的，我记得你。
Yeah, I remember you.
你在说什么，宝贝?
What are you talking about, baby?
只有爸爸办公室的那个白痴。
Oh, just that one idiot from Dad's office.
你是爸爸的朋友，对吧?
You're Dad's friend, right?
是的。你爸爸和我…我们非常接近。
Yes. Your dad and I are... We're very close.
我以为你…
I thought that you...
怎么了,妈妈?
What's wrong, Mom?
没什么,只是……我知道的东西。
Nothing, just... something I knew.
你知道吗?
You know what?
我本来想晚点再说的，但是…为什么不呢?
I was gonna save this for later, but... why not?
今天是你的生日，对吗?
It's your birthday, right?
-给你带了个礼物。——哦。
- Got a present for you. - Oh.
嘿,某人!
Hey, somebody!
求你了，帮我找到我的家人。
Please, help me find my family.
我要找到我的女儿。
I need to find my daughter.
有人知道吗?
Anyone?
你女儿穿的是粉色夹克吗?
Hey, your daughter, was she wearing a pink jacket?
-你在哪里看到她的?-一个警官把她和另一个人带到了那里。
- Yeah, where'd you see her? - An officer took her and another person up there.
——电梯。-我的天啊
- That elevator. - Oh, my God.
-他们要去屋顶。——让我们看。
- They're going to the roof. - Let's look.
我们走吧!走了!
Let's go! Walk!
走了!你的离开。
Walk! To your left.
很好。好了,停止。
Good. Okay, stop.
不,请!
No, please!
闭嘴!在那里。在那里。
Shut up! Get over there. Over there.
现在，你就把它想象成一件烟火夹克。
Now, you just think of this as a little fireworks jacket.
好吧?
Okay?
整个城市都会为你庆祝生日!
The whole city's gonna celebrate your birthday!
我们走吧。
Let's go.
更多的间接伤害!
More collateral damage!
要为你牺牲多少人，奥兰多!
How many gotta die for you, Orlando?!
哇!
Whoo!
所以我们终于到达了河的尽头。
So we finally reach the end of the river.
威拉德千里迢迢带着极端的偏见来消灭库尔茨上校，结果却发现……当他们遇到了……他们是同一个人。
Willard came all this way to eliminate Colonel Kurtz with extreme prejudice, only to find out... when they met... they were the same man.
来吧，奥兰多!面对你的指挥官!
Come on out, Orlando! Face your commanding officer!
好吧。好吧。
Okay. Okay.
我出来。
I'm coming out.
爸爸来了。
Here comes Daddy.
停!
Stop!
奥兰多，请解决这个问题。拜托!
Orlando, please fix this. Please!
你乱糟糟的。
You fucked up.
我计划周密，执行周密，士兵。
I had a well-planned, well-executed operation, soldier.
跟踪，监视，每天听你的嗡嗡声。
Tracking, surveillance, listening to your droning bullshit every fucking day.
神……他在家也那么无聊吗?
God... is he that boring at home?
我差一点就成功了。
I was so close.
你知道我为此付出了多少吗!
Do you have any idea what I put into this?!
建那个椅架花了多长时间!
How long it took to build that chair rig?!
是啊，你从哪学的?史泰登岛?
Yeah, where'd you learn that? On Staten Island?
嗯…当你老爸还在…三角洲的不结盟运动。
Well... you learn a thing or two when your old man was... Delta in 'Nam.
你的整个人生就是个谎言。
Your whole life is a lie.
你好的,亲爱的?
You good, honey?
你也许没朝我爸的脑袋开一枪，但你他妈的让他失去了工作!
You may not have put the bullet in my dad's head, but you fucking took him out of commission!
他和我妈妈…看着我!
He and my mom... Look at me!
好吧,好吧。
Okay, okay.
他们把所有的钱都投给了你那个冒牌公司。
They sunk every penny they had into that sham company of yours.
你说谎了。
You lied.
你还不如自己扣动扳机。
You might as well have pulled the trigger yourself.
奥兰多……我想让你知道…这是你应得的。
Orlando... I need you to know... You deserve this.
这都是因为你爸爸吗?
So this is all about your dad?
我的意思是，是也不是。我确实需要你的技能。
I mean, yes and no. I did need your skills.
杀了你，你知道，那只是…小咖啡馆。
Killing you, you know, that was just a... little perk.
这是我的罪，不是他们的。
This is my sin, not theirs.
父亲的罪孽…-放他们走-爸爸，我害怕!
The sins of the father... - Hey, let 'em go. - Dad, I'm scared!
带我。我可以帮你。我可以帮你消失。
Take me. I can help you. I can help you vanish.
不，我觉得这变成了自杀任务。
Nah, I think this just became a suicide mission.
爸爸，我想回家。
Dad, I wanna go home.
-我们会的，亲爱的-别再骗她了
- We will, honey. - Quit lying to her.
别再骗你女儿了!这就是你来这里的原因!
Quit lying to your daughter! That's what got you here!
你的欺骗，你的谎言!你他妈的蛇!
Your deceit, your lies! You fucking snake!
别撒谎!
Stop lying!
你知道吗，恩佐?你是对的。
You know what, Enzo? You're right.
我很喜欢它。
I enjoyed it.
我很享受这种忙碌。
I enjoyed the rush.
我很擅长这个。
I was good at it.
我很擅长。
I am good at it.
我还会这么做。
And I would do it again.
尤其是对你老爸这样的笨蛋。
Especially to a sucker like your old man.
你他妈闭嘴!
Shut the fuck up!
亲爱的,你明白吗?
Honey, you okay?
你对吧?
You all right?
好吧,好吧。好了，我们把这东西拿下来。
Okay, okay. Okay, let's get this thing off of you.
——好吧?-奥兰多，把它弄下来。
- All right? - Orlando, get it off.
爸爸……等一下,放松。
Dad... Hang on, relax.
-倒计时了。-哦,不。
- It's counting down. - Oh, no.
救命!
Help! Help!
你打算怎么办?
What are you gonna do?
你打算怎么办，奥兰多?
What are you gonna do, Orlando?
再责怪自己吗?
Blame yourself again?
跑
Run.
我哪也不去。我呆在这里。去,金。走吧!
I'm not going anywhere. I'm staying here. Go, Kim. Go!
——不。——走!
- No. - Go!
——不。-跑…
- No. - Run...
将军。
Checkmate.
谢谢你！
Thank you!
谢谢，谢谢，谢谢。
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
是的，我在路上了。医院见
Yeah, I'm on my way. See you at the hospital.
是啊，度假听起来不错。
Yeah, a vacation sounds nice.
退休听起来更好。
Retirement sounds better.
是的。
Yep.
谢谢你的帮忙。
Thanks for helping out.
是啊，我只是个想修复家庭的人。
Yeah, I'm just a guy trying to fix his family.
那边那个人，他是英雄。
That guy over there, he's the hero.
他拯救了我们所有人。
He saved us all.
把这话告诉报纸，好吗?
Tell that to the papers, okay?
我们需要你去局里问话。
We're gonna need you downtown for questioning.
我能和家人单独待一会儿吗?
Can I just have a minute with my family?
是的。
Yeah.
你们还在为我错过派对而生气吗?
You guys still mad at me for missing the party?
我是来补偿你的，好吗?
I'm here to make it up to you, okay?